I'm going to be tackling this coding task by following these four steps.
我将按照以下四步来完成这一编程任务
So first, we'll need to update the word class to store the audio
首先我们需要更新 Word 类来为每个单词
information for each word.
存储音频信息
After that, we will need to update the way that the list of words are created.
接着 我们需要更新单词列表的创建方式
Following, we'll need to update the OnItemClickListener
然后 我们需要更新 OnItemClickListener
to play the correct sound file when an item is clicked on.
当列表项被点击时 能播放正确的声音文件
And then lastly, for now I'm going to focus on the numbers activity but
最后 我们一直针对的是 NumbersActivity
then we're going to repeat the process for all our other categories.
但是现在我们将为所有其他类别重复相同的流程
Now here in our world class, I want to start by adding an integer variable
打开 Word 类 首先我将添加一个整型变量
that we can use to store an Audio Resource ID.
用来存储音频资源 ID
Now, this will just be the resource ID that we reference,
我们将通过该资源 ID
where the actual audio file can be found.
找到实际的音频文件所在的位置
And notice here, that I've called it mAudioResourceId.
注意这里 我称其为 mAudioResourceId
Then, I want to modify the word constructors to accept another input,
然后我需要修改 Word 构造函数来接受另一个输入值
in order to set the audio field.
以便设置音频字段
So I'm going to add it to both constructors because all words will have
我将其添加到两个构造函数中 因为所有的单词
to have an audio file, regardless of whether they have an image or not.
都需要具有一个音频文件 无论是否具有图片
Then, I'm going to set the member variable mAudioResourceId
然后我将成员变量 mAudioResourceId
to be equal to the audio parameter that was passed in.
设为等于传入的音频参数
Now every time you modify the constructor,
每次修改构造函数时
remember to update the java.comment.
都要记得更新 java 注释
That way, any other developers who are calling the constructor
这样其他调用该构造函数的开发者
knows what inputs to pass in.
就能知道要传入什么输入值
Since we declared the audio variable to be private
因为我们将 Audio 变量声明为私有变量
we should create a public getter method.
所以应该创建一个公共的 getter 方法
Just like we created public methods for other classes in order to access
就像我们为其他类创建了公共方法
the English and Miwok strings, as well as the Image Resource ID.
以便访问英语和米沃克字符串以及 ImageResourceId 一样
So, I want to make a public method here, the returns an Integer Resource ID and
我要在这里创建一个公共方法 返回整型 ResourceId
I'm going to name the method getAudioResourceId.
我将该方法称为 getAudioResourceId
There are going to be no input requirements and
该方法没有输入参数
the method will just return the private audio variable.
直接返回私有 Audio 变量
Also, since it's a public method, I'm going to add a comment to
因为它是公共方法 我为该方法添加一条注释
the method just to clarify what the purpose of it is.
解释下它的作用是什么
All right, so those were all the changes we need to make the word class.
这些就是我们需要对 Word 类做出的所有更改
So, now we have a new private audio variable and it's set
现在我们具有了一个新的私有 Audio 变量
via the two constructors, and we have a public method to access that variable.
通过两个构造函数进行了设置 我们具有一个公共方法来访问该变量
All right,so that finished off our first step, and
第一步就完成了
since we modified the word class constructors,
我们修改了 Word 类构造函数
we'll need to modify the places that we use those constructors.
需要修改下使用这些构造函数的地方
So, for example in the NumbersActivity, the FamilyActivity, and
例如 在 NumbersActivity FamilyActivity
all the other activities.
以及所有其他 Activity 中
So there we need to change how the word objects are created.
在这些 Activity 中 我们需要更改 Word 对象的创建方式
Now in the numbers activity, we created an array list of words and
在 NumbersActivity 中 我们创建了一个单词数组列表
each word was created with three arguments.
每个单词都具有三个参数
So first, the English word, the Miwok word, and then the image.
第一个是英语单词 第二个是米沃克单词 最后一个是图片
Now we need to add a fourth argument which will be the resource ID
现在我们需要添加第四个参数 即与该单词相关的音频文件的
of the audio file that goes along with the word.
资源 ID
So for the number 1, I'm going to add R.raw.number_1.
对于数字一 我将添加 R.raw.number_1
And as you can see here, Android Studio is smart enough to automatically suggest
在这里可以看到 Android Studio 非常智能 能够自动提示
the files that have been added to the Raw folder already,
已经添加到 Raw 文件夹中的文件
just in case I forget what the resources were named.
以防我忘记了资源的名称
Now for the number 2, I'm going to add R.raw.number_2.
对于数字二 我将添加 R.raw.number_2
So I'm going to copy and paste and make modifications for
我将为剩余的几个数字复制粘贴这些代码
the rest of the ten numbers.
并稍加修改
And this is what the code should look like when all the words have
当所有单词都具有音频资源 ID 后
an Audio Resource ID.
代码应该是这样的
So the rest of the code in the numbers activity can continue using the words
NumbersActivity 中剩余的代码可以继续
array list as before.
像之前一样使用单词数组列表
Now, I want to make the updates to the other categories so
现在我将对其他类别做出更新
that they use the right constructor.
使它们都使用正确的构造函数
I when I open up a PhrasesActivity, I see that there are errors showing up.
当我打开 PhrasesActivity 时 我发现这里出现了错误
And this is because that there are no valid word constructors for
这是因为 没有只有两个输入参数的有效
just two inputs anymore.
Word 构造函数了
So let's make some changes to get rid these errors.
我们做出一些更改 解决这些错误
So here's what the words list should look like when each word
这是当每个单词都使用正确的三个输入参数构造函数时
is using the correct three input constructor.
单词列表所具有的最终代码
Now remember, if the line of code exceeds a 100 columns,
注意 如果代码行超过 100 列
we should wrap the text to the next line and then indent by 8 spaces.
我们应该将文本换到下一行 并缩进 8 个空格
Also, note here that the ArrayList is now final.
注意 ArrayList 现在被声明为 final
So I want to make similar changes to our FamilyActivity and our ColorsActivity.
现在我将对 FamilyActivity 和 ColorsActivity 做出类似的更改
And here's what the finished code looks like for the FamilyActivity and
这是 FamilyActivity 和 ColorsActivity 完成更改后的
the ColorsActivity.
最终代码
All right, so now the word class has been updated,
现在 Word 类被更新了
as well as the places that we call the word class constructor.
以及调用 Word 类构造函数的地方也被更新了
Next, we're going to update the OnItemClickListener so
现在 我们将更新 OnItemClickListener
that it plays the correct audio file.
使其播放正确的音频文件
In the NumberActivity, I'm going to modify the code for
在 NumberActivity 中我将修改当列表项被点击时
when a list item gets clicked on.
出现的行为对应的代码
So right now, we always play the same number_one MP3 file.
现在 我们始终播放的都是相同的 number_one MP3 文件
Let's insert some code above it.
我们在上面插入一些代码
But first we need to figure out which word is getting clicked on and
首先我们需要弄明白哪个单词被点击了
then store that in a variable.
然后将其存储在一个变量中
So from the onItemClick method position parameter,
通过 onItemClick 方法的 position 参数
I can check the words array list to get the word that was clicked on.
我可以检查下 Words ArrayList 获取被点击的单词
So, to do that, I can just call words.get and
为此 我可以调用 words.get()
pass in the position variable.
并传入 position 变量
So, this method will return a single word variable, I can go ahead and
该方法将返回一个 Word 变量
store that variable on the left-hand side here.
我可以将该变量存储在左侧
Now, if you get a red squiggle under here indicating an error, and
如果这里出现了红色的曲线 表示出错了
the error says something like variable words is accessed from within and
错误消息类似于变量 Words 无法从内部访问
enter class needs to be declared final.
类需要声明为 final
Remember, that means that we need to declare the words ArrayList as final, so
注意 这意味着我们需要将 words ArrayList 声明为 final
double check that you have the set as final up here.
请再次检查下你是否在这里声明为 final
So, once I know what word is clicked on,
当我知道哪个单词被点击后
I can get the Audio Resource ID of it and then pass that into the MediaPlayer.
我就可以获取该单词的 AudioResourceId 然后将其传入 MediaPlayer
So, that means I can delete this R.raw.number_one that we've
这意味着我可以删除这里硬编码的 R.raw.number_one
hard coded in here, and just use word.getAudioResourceId.
直接使用 word.getAudioResourceId
There we go, and that should work.
就是这样 应该是可行的
So, once the MediaPlayer is created, we can start playing the audio file.
创建 MediaPlayer 后 我们可以开始播放音频文件了
Now I'm going to add in some comments as well here, so
我将在这里也添加一些注释
we remember what's going on.
以便记住这里的操作
So that finished off our third step.
第三步就完成了
Now the last step is to make sure that it works for
第四步是确保剩余的类别 Activity
the rest of the category activities.
也是可行的
Now, to make the FamilyActivity work, I copied over the MediaPlayer variable
为了使 FamilyActivity 可行 我复制了 MediaPlayer 变量
as well as the code for the setOnItemClickListener.
以及 setOnItemClickListener 的代码
Remember that when you copy and paste,
注意 在复制粘贴时
make sure to grab the final curly brace, closing parentheses, and semi-colon too.
确保带上最后的大括号 右括号以及分号
Also, I made the words ArrayList final so
同时 我将 Words ArrayList 声明为 final
that I can reference it within the item ClickListener.
以便在 itemClickListener 中引用它
Now the media player needs to reference the activity context,
现在 MediaPlayer 需要引用相应的 Activity Context
so I changed it from the NumbersActivity to the FamilyActivity,
所以我将其从 NumbersActivity 改成了 FamilyActivity
because that's the activity that we're currently in.
因为这是我们当前所处的 Activity
And then I repeated the same process for the Colors class, and one more time for
然后为 Colors 类重复相同的流程
the PhrasesActivity.
然后再为 PhrasesActivity 重复一次
Now hopefully, after setting this up several times, you're getting the hang
希望在多次设置后 你已经开始明白
of setting up ItemClickListeners as well as using the MediaPlayer.
如何设置 ItemClickListener 以及如何使用 MediaPlayer
Now let's demo the app, and we should be able to hear Andrea's voice for
现在我们来演示下应用 对于所有单词 我们都应该能够听到
all the words.
Andrea 的发音
So, let's start with Phrases this time.
这次我们从 Phrases 开始
&gt;&gt; [FOREIGN] &gt;&gt; Nice.
- [米沃克语] - 不错
And then go to Colors.
然后转到 Colors
&gt;&gt; [FOREIGN] &gt;&gt; Sounds good so far.
- [米沃克语] - 目前听起来不错
Now to Family Members.
现在转到 Family Members
&gt;&gt; [FOREIGN] &gt;&gt; And lastly,
- [米沃克语] - 最后
our good old Numbers Activity.
转到我们的 NumbersActivity
&gt;&gt; [FOREIGN] &gt;&gt; Perfect.
- [米沃克语] - 很不错
So I want to take a moment and
我想停下来
congratulate you on all the hard work that you've done.
对你一直以来的努力表示祝贺
So you've reached a really big milestone by incorporating all these features
你完成了里程碑式的成就 将所有这些功能都添加到了该应用中
into this app, as well as learn so many new skills along the way.
并且一路以来 学到了很多新的技能
So take a moment and give yourselves a pat on the back.
停下来 表扬下自己吧
And then go show off your app to your friends and family.
然后向亲朋好友展示下你的应用吧
We're really proud of you and you deserve it.
我们太为你感到骄傲了 你值得我们的表扬